

Elizabeth House, First Floor, Block 2, 39 York Road, London, SE1 7NQ Tel: +44 (0)20 7378 7300 Fax: +44 (0)20 7183 1899

 $\pmb{Email: \underline{consultant@londonresearchinternational.com}}\\$

www.LondonResearchInternational.com

Ms. Kar

NATIONALITY: Malaysian

SUMMARY

During my study, I am a member in computational fluid mechanic majoring in flow analysis and I already taken these subjects in my master degree (Instruments, CAD, Finite Element Analysis, Energy Management, CFD, Vibration, Shell Plate and Pressure Vessel, Fluid Mechanic, Control, Design Optimization, Structural Vibration, and Advanced Engineering Mathematics).

I work as an Engineer specialising in rotating equipment during my last employment at Construction and Commissioning of Plant Rejuvenation and Revamp 2 (PRR2) for Gas Processing Plant 2 (GPP2), Gas Processing Plant 3 (GPP3), Export Terminal Unit 3 and 4 (ET3&4) and Kerteh Compressor Station A for Petronas Gas Berhad

EDUCATION

- 2008-2009 Malaysia University of Technology, Malaysia
 Master in Mechanical Engineering
- 2000-2003 Mara University of Technology, Malaysia
 BSc (hons) in Mechanical Engineering
- 1996-1999 Malaysia University of Technology, Malaysia
 Diploma in Aeronautical Engineering

EMPLOYMENT RECORD / PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

PFCE (Hyundai) Offshore Worldwide Sdn Bhd, Kerteh Terengganu, Malaysia



Elizabeth House, First Floor, Block 2, 39 York Road, London, SE1 7NQ Tel: +44 (0)20 7378 7300 Fax: +44 (0)20 7183 1899

Email: consultant@londonresearchinternational.com

www.LondonResearchInternational.com

Position : Engineer (piping & mechanical)

Duration : April 2007-October 2012

Work Description

Project Involved:- Provision of Engineering, Procurement, Construction and Commissioning of Plant Rejuvenation and Revamp 2 (PRR2) for Gas Processing Plant 2 (GPP2), Gas Processing Plant 3 (GPP3), Export Terminal Unit 3 and 4 (ET3&4) and Kerteh Compressor Station A for Petronas Gas Berhad.

Scope of Activity:

- Prepare MTO (Material Take Off)
- Assist on preparation of workpack
- Ensure material are delivered on time and right location
- Monitor fabrication progress
- Liaise with client for shutdown preparation.
- Check drawing (P & ID & ISO).
- Identify location for execution team.
- Monitor tagging (ensure the tag no is showed)
- Familiar with ASME, ANSI and PTS code.
- Identify reliable type of pipe support.
- Prepare report / documentation for closing pack.
- Design and prepare the detail drawing for mechanical, piping and structure, P&ID, chart and/or scale drawing for compact project from observation, measurement, sketches and specification.
- Structure analysis for failure and safety factor

Malaysia Aviation Training Academy, Malaysia

Malaysia Aviation Training Academy is a family of, Aviasian Sdn Bhd.

Position : Technical Instructor

Duration : 02 Oct 2006 – 01 Jan 2007

Work Description :

• To develop student's basic technical skills (ie: Maths, Physics & Technical Drawing).



Elizabeth House, First Floor, Block 2, 39 York Road, London, SE1 7NQ Tel: +44 (0)20 7378 7300 Fax: +44 (0)20 7183 1899

Email: consultant@londonresearchinternational.com www.LondonResearchInternational.com

- Assists Training Department's functions in preparing the syllabus and module according to the requirements stated by DCA (BCAR & JAR 66)
- Conduct training /laboratories sessions.
- Access students evaluate, test and analyze students' performance Impart hands on practical training skill.

Aviasi Industri Sdn Bhd, Malaysia

Aviasi Industry is a family of, Aviasian Sdn Bhd

Position : Mechanical Engineer

Duration : 02 Feb 2005 – 01Oct 2006

Work Description :

- To produce mechanical Design for ground support equipment based on Aviation Industry MIG 29.
- To ensure that the products are verified and have fulfilled the clients' requirements

Aviasian Sdn Bhd, Malaysia

Position : Engineer

Duration : 29 Sept 2003 – 02 Feb 2005

Work Description :

- Responsible in providing technical and product applications services to customers such as ATSC, Airod, Fire Brigade Air Wing, Royal Malaysian Army Air Wing (PUTD), Royal Malaysian Navy Air Wing and others.
- Proposal and prepare tender application.
- Ensure the delivery of Ground Support Equipment (GSE) and MIG-29 spare parts to customers as scheduled.
- An effective member in company road shows, international events (ie: LIMA, DSA, ASEAN Aerospace)

• TR Technology Sdn Bhd, Malaysia

Duration: 10th May - 24th July 2001

Work Description : Practical trainee

Inspection, measurement, equipment diagnostic techniques skills and new maintenance technology knowledge .Basic knowledge in pneumatic and



Elizabeth House, First Floor, Block 2, 39 York Road, London, SE1 7NQ Tel: +44 (0)20 7378 7300 Fax: +44 (0)20 7183 1899

 $\label{lemail:consultant@londonresearch international.com} \\ \underline{ www.LondonResearch International.com} \\ \\ \underline{ www.LondonResearch International.com} \\ \\ \\ \\ \underline{ www.LondonResearch International.com} \\ \\ \underline{ www.LondonResearch International.com} \\ \\ \underline{ www.LondonResearch International.com} \\ \underline{ www.LondonResearch International.$

hydraulics. Specialized maintenance machine and equipment repair skills.

• Celcom Malaysia Berhad, Malaysia

Duration: 1st December 1999 - 14th April 2000

Work Description : Practical trainee

Management and quality improvement research and development -

Communications system

PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATIONS	
n/a	
PUBLICATIONS	
n/a	

English, Malay

LANGUAGES